Guide to the Goddard Lieberson Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1939-1977
  - Correspondence by subject
    - Dartmouth College, 1967-1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Dartmouth College, 1975-1977 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Dartmouth College, 1973-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Harlem Opera House Rebuilding Project, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Invitations, No Date (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Invitations, 1970-1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Invitations, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Invitations, 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Invitations, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Invitations, 1974 (Box 29a, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1974 (Box 29a, Folder 2)
    - Invitations, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Jamaica Vacation with Eugene Ormandy (1956) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Letters of Congratulations -- Musical Director of Columbia Masterworks, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Letters of Congratulations - CBS VP, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Letters to G.L. during illness, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Letters of Congratulations - CBS Presidency, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Letters of Congratulations - CBS Presidency, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Promotion Thank-you Correspondence, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Residence and Piano, 247 E. 61st Street, 1967-1975 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Payola International, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Peter Lieberson, 1962-1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Retirement, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Santa Fe, 1970-1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Sculpture, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - String Quartet (by G.L.), 1963 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Tailor, 1969-1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Works Progress Administration, 1935-1937 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Vera Zorina, 1962-1968 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Vera Zorina, 1973-1977 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Vera Zorina, 1944-1959 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Vera Zorina, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Vera Zorina, Condolence letters, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Vera Zorina, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Vera Zorina, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Vera Zorina, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Vera Zorina, 1978-1989 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Vera Zorina - G.L. Memorial, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Yale Music Library - American Musical Theater Collection, 1955-1960 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence by date, 1974-1977
    The Correspondence by Date subseries is made up of a smaller group of dated correspondence from Lieberson's last years at the firm, until his death (c. 1974-1977).
    This group of correspondence is very similar to the material in the previous two subseries. However, this group of letters was found together in a binder, and the decision was made to keep this arrangement.
    - January - April 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - April - July 1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - January - June 1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - June - December 1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - January - May 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - May - December 1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - January - December 1977 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Photographs, 1920-1975
  The Photographs Series includes black-and-white and color photographs. Subjects range from posed portraits of Goddard Lieberson to casual snapshots of family vacations. The "photo albums" subseries contains candid, professional-quality photographs depict Lieberson with various musicians and composers, often in the studio. These include artists such as Leonard Bernstein, Johnny Cash, Miles Davis, John Geilgud, Rex Harrison, Ethel Merman, Cole Porter, Igor Stravinsky and Teddy Wilson.
  - Work
    - Goddard Lieberson alone
      Each folder contains 10 photographs. The photographs are not in chronological order.
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Goddard Lieberson alone (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Goddard Lieberson with others
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 1)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 2)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 3)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 4)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 5)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 6)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 7)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 8)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 9)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 10)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 11)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 12)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 13)
      - Goddard Lieberson with others (Box 35A, Folder 14)
    - Photo albums, 1956-1963 (Box 36)
      - "For Goddard Lieberson, Remembrance of Things Past - Christmas 1956", 28 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - "Goddard's Way, Christmas 1957", 19 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - "The Liebersons, Christmas 1958", 26 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - "To Goddard Lieberson, The Past Recaptured - Christmas 1959", 20 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - For Goddard Lieberson, 1960 Recaptured", 44 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - "Goddard Lieberson, 1961, 1962, 1963", 30 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - "Goddard LIeberson, 1961, 1962, 1963", 16 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Photographs with dedications and photos of others (Box 37)
      This subseries includes photos with dedications to Goddard Lieberson from various colleagues and artists. Also included is one folder of photographs of others.
  - Personal, 1920-1975
    This subseries consists of roughly 300 snapshots - black and white, as well as color. A set of color slides is also included in this subseries. Although many of the photos are not identified, they depict family, friends and vacations.
    - Family Snapshots
      - Family snapshots (Box 35A, Folder 15)
      - Family snapshots (Box 35A, Folder 16)
      - Family snapshots (Box 38)
        This box contains circa 300 snapshots of Goddard Lieberson and his family, including his wife Brigitta, his sons Peter and Jonathan, and other (unidentified) relatives. Additional family snapshots can be found in Box 35A, folders 15 and 16.
    - Slides (Box 39)
      Contains roughly 100 color slides of Goddard Lieberson and his family.
- Business files, 1948-1978
  This series contains a variety of materials related to Columbia Records and Columbia Foundation, Inc. (CFI). Sources include meeting notes for CFI, Lieberson's travel itineraries, and correspondence documenting Columbia's relationships with arts organizations across the country. With the exception of a few recording projects from the late 1940s, the material in this series dates from Lieberson's last decade as president of Columbia Records.
  The files are arranged alphabetically within each subseries, except for the travel documents, which are organized by date.
  - Columbia Projects
    This subseries contains materials relating to select projects Lieberson either oversaw or participated in, between 1948 and 1978. Documents include correspondence, research sources, and other materials pertaining to Columbia's production and release of particular recordings. Included are recording projects from the "Legacy" series: "I Can Hear it Now" (1948), "The Union" and "The Confederacy" (1956), as well as recordings of Lieberson's String Quartet and Piano Pieces. The files here do not necessarily contain all available documentation of these projects, in which case the researcher is advised to consult related personal correspondence files, as well.
    Arranged alphabetically according to project title.
    - The Adventures of Pippin (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - As We Remember Him (JFK Album), 1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - As We Remember Him (JFK Album) Liner Notes (Oversized), 1964 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Handwritten re-writings
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Narrative Text
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      notes
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      Diaghilev Research
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      Typescripts and edits
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Book materials
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Book notes and correspondence
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Notes and research
    - Ballet (Legacy Series), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      Research notes and sources
    - Billy, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Black Music in America (Legacy Series), 1968-1969 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Bye Bye Birdie, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Charles Ives, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - A Chorus Line, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Columbia Broadcasting Symphony (Radio Show), 1943 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - The Confederacy and The Union, 1956-1957 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - The Confederacy and The Union, 1956-1957 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Cresta Blanca Carnival (Radio Show), 1943 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Cresta Blanca Carnival (Radio Show), 1943 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Cry of the Peacock (Ardèle ou la Marguerite), 1948 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Homage to Handel, 1965-1966 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - I Can Hear it Now, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Igor Stravinsky (Legacy Series), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Invitation to Music (Radio Show), 1943 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Irving Berlin (Legacy Series), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Kurt Weill and Lotte Lenya Tribute, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Legacy Series (Box 42, Folder 15)
      General notes and correspondence
    - A Little Night Music, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Medicine, Mind, and Music, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Medicine, Mind, and Music, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Medicine, Mind, and Music, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Modern American Music Series, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - My Fair Lady, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - My Fair Lady, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - My Fair Lady (China), 1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - New York Philharmonic Radio (Radio Show), 1943-01-1943-03 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - New York Philharmonic Radio (Radio Show), 1943 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - "Piano Pieces" (Lieberson composition), 1964-1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Pleasure Dome, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Prudential Family Hour (Radio Show), 1948 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - "String Quartet" (Lieberson composition), 1962-1965 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Tenth Anniversary Record, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - They Said It With Music: Yankee Doodle to Ragtime (Panorama of American History Through Its Music), 1977 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - They Said It With Music: Yankee Doodle to Ragtime (Panorama of American History Through Its Music), 1977 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - They Said It With Music: Yankee Doodle to Ragtime (Panorama of American History Through Its Music), 1977 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - They Said It With Music: Yankee Doodle to Ragtime (Panorama of American History Through Its Music), 1977 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - They Said It With Music: Yankee Doodle to Ragtime (Panorama of American History Through Its Music), 1977 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - They Said It With Music: Yankee Doodle to Ragtime (Panorama of American History Through Its Music), 1977 (Box 44a, Folder 1)
    - They Said It With Music: Yankee Doodle to Ragtime (Panorama of American History Through Its Music), 1977 (Box 44a, Folder 2)
    - They Said It With Music: Yankee Doodle to Ragtime (Panorama of American History Through Its Music), 1977 (Box 44a, Folder 3)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, 1963 (Box 44a, Folder 4)
    - Who's Who in America, 1966-1967 (Box 44a, Folder 5)
    - Lists of Goddard Lieberson Recording Projects (Box 44a, Folder 6)
    - CBS Gold Records Documentation, 1939-1974 (Box 44a, Folder 7)
    - Grammy Awards Documentation, 1974 (Box 44a, Folder 8)
  - Columbia Foundation Incorporated (CFI)
    These files contain materials relating to Lieberson's last decade at the firm (c. 1965-1975), when he served as a member of the Board of the Columbia Foundation, Inc. (CFI). The documents range from board meeting notes (compiled in large folders, organized by meeting date) to correspondence and inter-Columbia business memos dealing with matters relating to the board or to the larger corporation. In general, these business materials differ from other Columbia business files in that they involve memberships and donations relating to CFI, not to Columbia Masterworks or Columbia Records. For correspondence and materials relating to recording projects, the researcher should consult the Columbia Projects sub-series or the correspondence series.
    Board meetings organized by date. Correspondence and institutional memberships organized alphabetically by subject.
    - Board meetings
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1972-02-09 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1972-03-08 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1972-04-12 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1972-06-14 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1972-08-09 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1973-02-14 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1973-04-11 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1973-06-13 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - "Mr. Lieberson", 1973-10-10 (Box 45a, Folder 1)
      - "Committee on Cultural Activities, Goddard Lieberson", 1974-11-11 (Box 45a, Folder 2)
      - "Goddard Lieberson", 1974-02-13 (Box 45a, Folder 3)
      - "Committee on Cultural Activities, Goddard Lieberson", 1974-07-17 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - "CBS Foundation, Inc., Goddard Lieberson", 1974-09-11 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - "CBS Foundation, Inc., Goddard Lieberson", 1974-10-09 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - "CBS Foundation, Inc., Goddard Lieberson", 1974-12-11 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - "Committee on Cultural Activities, Goddard Lieberson", 1975-01-10 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - "CBS Foundation, Inc., Committee on Cultural Affairs, Goddard Lieberson", 1975-03-12 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - "CBS Foundation, Inc., Goddard Lieberson", 1975-05-13 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Assorted correspondence, memos and budget documents
      - A + R (Artists and Repertoire), 1954; 1962 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Business Directories, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 4)
        Contains two business directories: one printed from 1951 and a second handwritten from c. 1965
      - CBS Book Library Orders (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - CBS Foundation, 1973-04 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - CBS Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - CBS Foundation - Arts Comm. Meeting, 1972-08 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - CBS Foundation - Arts Comm. Meeting, 1972-11 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - CBS Foundation - Arts Comm. Meeting, 1973-01 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - CBS Foundation - Corporate Management (Misc.), 1972 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - CBS Foundation - Division Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - CBS Foundation - Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - CBS Foundation - Notes on Film Companies, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - CFI/Sony, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - CFI Foundation, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - IFPI, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Positions, 1956-1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
        Documents relating to job descriptions at Columbia, including Lieberson's presidency and his announcement regarding retirement
      - Record Catalogs - Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 2B)
      - Sony, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Sony Music/Family Club, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Sony/Kwai/Family Club, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Sony, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Viacom Information, 1971-1973 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Institutional memberships, donations and collaborations - from CFI files
      This subseries contains institutional correspondence and other documents relevant to Goddard Lieberson's participation in non-CBS organizations and companies. Topics include membership, board meetings, donations, events, and projects supported by Columbia. In addition to correspondence, folders contain copies of meeting notes, business materials for board members, public statements about institutional objectives, and details about cultural projects or festivals. Note that institutional names found in this subseries overlap with those listed in the "Named Correspondence" subseries.
      - CFI - Actor's Studio, Inc. (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - American Center of P.E.N (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - American Place Theater (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Business Com. for the Arts (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Children's Art Carnival (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Circle in the Square (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Constance Hope Associates (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - City Center Acting Company (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - City Center of Music and Drama (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Colondes Theater Lab (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Community Film Workshop Council, Inc. (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Company Contributions (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - The Composers Ensemble (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Composers Lyricists Educational Foundation (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Concert Artists Guild (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Corcoran Gallery of Art (Box 48, Folder 25)
      - Dance Theater of Harlem (Box 48, Folder 26)
      - Diller-Quaile School of Music, Inc. (Box 48, Folder 27)
      - Folger Shakespeare Library (Box 48, Folder 28)
      - George Peabody College (Box 48, Folder 29)
      - Harlem Theater and Workshop, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Harlem Theater and Workshop, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Harlem Theater and Workshop, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Harlem Theater and Workshop, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Harlem Theater and Workshop, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Harlem Theater and Workshop, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Harlem Theater and Workshop Board Meeting (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Horticultural Society of NY (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Institute of New Cinema Artists (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Jazzmobile, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Manhattan Theater Club (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Manhattan Theater Club, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Phoenix Theater (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Professional Children's School (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Manhattan Country School (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Manhattan School of Music (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Merry Mini Players, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Museum of the City of New York (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Museum of Modern Art (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Musicians Emergency Fund (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - National Book Committee, Inc. (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - NET Opera (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - National Music Council, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - Eugene O'Neil Memorial Theater (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Opera Association of New Mexico (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - George Peabody College (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - Performing Arts Group (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - Speculum Musicae (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - Stuart Ostrow Foundation (Box 49, Folder 30)
      - Symphony of the New World (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - Theater Development Fund (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - Theater for Ideas, Inc. (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - Urban Arts Corps. (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - Young Audiences, Inc. (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - Young Filmaker's Foundation (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Institutional memberships, donations and collaborations
    [the only difference between this and the previous sub-sub-series description is that these files did not come from CFI files.]
    The documents are organized alpahbetically according to organization name.
    - Alban Berg Society (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - American Library Association (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - American Music Center (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - American Orchestra for Contemporary Music (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - ASCAP, 1966-1975 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - ASCAP (oversized) (Box 81, Folder 4)
      Certificate of elected membership
    - Amnesty International (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Study (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Association Robert Casadesus (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Bedside Network (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Century Association (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Circle in the Square Theater (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - City Center Music and Orchestra (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Civil War Round Table (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Country Music Foundation (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Donation Correspondence, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Duke Ellington Center for Cancer Care (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Entertainment Hall of Fame (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Friends of Maurice Ravel (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - George Henry Foundation (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Kennedy Center, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Library and Museum of Performing Arts (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Lincoln Center, 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Lincoln Center, 1969-1972 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Opera, 1972-1975 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Opera, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Music Theater of LC, 1968-1975 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1973-1976 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - New Orchestra, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - New York Film Festival, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - New York Jazz Museum, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - New York Philharmonic (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Philadelphia Orchestra (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Phoenix Theater (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Professional Children's School (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Professional Children's School, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Samuel Beckett Theater, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Santa Fe Opera (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Schweitzer Fellowship (Box 52, Folder 6)